eclaimsline.com 2011-06-29

# eClaims - Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions

The Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use set forth below provide you, the user, with a comprehensive description of this site's information and privacy practices and what constitutes acceptable expectations and behaviors relevant to the use of this site. By using this site, you acknowledge and agree to be bound by all of the terms and conditions set forth below. 

_To go directly to a specific section, please click on the link below_

  * Who or What Is EclaimsLine.com?  

  * Eclaims Privacy Policy  

  * What Information Will Be Collected?  

  * How Is Your Information Protected?  

  * Does Eclaims use Cookies?  

  * Use of Information  

  * Legal Disclaimer-Instances In Which Your Information May Be Disclosed  

  * Business Transfers  

  * Links to Other Web Sites  

  * You Have a Right To Update and Verify The Accuracy Of Information We Collect  

  * Sweepstakes, Trivia Games, and Surveys  

  * Contacting Eclaims  

  * Modification of This Privacy Policy  

  * You May Elect to Not Provide Information to Us Electronically  

  * Eclaims Terms and Conditions of Use  

  * Copyright  

  * No Warranties  

  * Modification of Terms and Conditions of Use  

Who or What Is EclaimsLine.com? 

EclaimsLine.com ("Eclaims") is an online claims center that enables Visa cardholders to take full advantage of the Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver Benefit provided on eligible cards . The Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver Benefit,, is made possible through the collaborative efforts of several business partners, all of whom are committed to serving you, the cardholder. The EClaims site is brought to you by the Benefit Administrator and not by Visa U.S.A. Inc. (“Visa”). Visa is not affiliated with Eclaims. 

You will notice links on this site that lead you back to the "Visa Home Page". This is because when you access Eclaims, you leave the Visa.com site. We provide these links because we understand that you may want to return to Visa.com once you have finished filing or checking the status of a claim. Please note that this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use, which follow, apply only to the Eclaims site. If accessing other web sites, including Visa.com, please be sure to consult the policies and terms of use specifically applicable to those sites. 

Throughout this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use you will see the words "you", "your" and "yours". These refer to you as a visitor to Eclaims and/or as the holder of a Visa card that entitles you to the Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver Benefit. You will also see "Eclaims", "we", "us" and "our". These refer to the Benefit Administrator. 

Eclaims Privacy Policy

* * *

We value our relationship with you. Protecting the privacy of information we collect about you is of great importance to us. We want you to understand how we protect the confidentiality of information about you as well as how and why we use and disclose it. The following provides details relating to our practices and procedures for protecting the security of your nonpublic personal information. Following this policy, you will also find a description of the terms and conditions related to your use of this site. If you are not satisfied with our privacy measures or do not agree with the terms and conditions set forth below, please discontinue your visit to Eclaims. In such instance, we strongly encourage you to share your concerns or questions with us, by emailing us at [privacy@mondialUSA.com](mailto:privacy@mondialUSA.com). Note that the following policy only applies to information collected on this web site, and not to any information we may obtain about you from other sources. 

What Information Will Be Collected? 

In the process of visiting Eclaims, you will be providing information. You provide information directly by entering it in yourself (e.g., your name, email address or other personal data). This includes the information you provide via the log in page, the online claims form, status inquiry pages and any emails you may send to us. The information you provide via the log in page allows us to personalize the site for you when you visit. All other information you provide, on this site enables us to better process and service your claim(s). 

You also provide information indirectly, in the form of data that is automatically collected by the web site. This may include our retaining a record of a user's entry and exit page points (in other words, the page on which you start your use of the site and the page from which you leave). This data, if collected, will not be personally connected to you and will only be collected in the aggregate, in order to assist us in creating a site that is easier and more convenient for you to use. 

We collect the information that you provide, both directly and indirectly, to assist with site development, to create usage reports, and to enhance claims servicing. We will not sell your personal information to third parties for any purposes, including, but not limited to: marketing or other consumer related mailings. However, because Eclaims is serviced collaboratively, we may share the information you provide among the companies that provide and support your Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver. For more information regarding this, please see the section below entitled "Use of Information". 

How Is Your Information Protected? 

_We are committed to ensuring that all of your EclaimsLine.com transactions are safe and secure and protected by VeriSign._. 

To ensure that every transaction is protected, we use advanced encryption technology; we treat your credit card and personal information with the highest standards of confidentiality and safety. To that end all such information about you, which is maintained on our server, is protected by the use of technologically advanced firewalls. We restrict access to your personal information to only the employees or agents of VISA, the underwriter, benefit administrator and the program quality assurance monitor, who need to know that information in order to service your account. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. 

By filing your claim on our secure server, you are further protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, utilized by most popular browsers, including Netscape and Microsoft Explorer. This technology allows us to use advanced encryption tools to protect information transmitted between your computer and our server. Once processed by Visa Travel Assist, your credit-card information is not transmitted over the Internet again. 

Does Eclaims use Cookies? 

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any personal information about you; instead they hold information a site may need to personalize your experience and to gather web site statistical data. This notwithstanding, Eclaims does not utilize cookie technology. 

Use of Information 

Non-personal information is collected to track the total number of guests visiting this site and to guide our efforts to improve our site. This information is used exclusively for our internal purposes and is not disclosed to any non-affiliated third parties. 

Personal information is information that can identify a visitor, such as name, address or policy information. You can be assured that when you file an Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver Benefit claim with us, we will only use your personal information to process your Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver Benefit claim. Except as otherwise set forth in this privacy policy notice, we will not disclose or sell any of your personal information, including your name, address, credit-card number, or claim history to any third party. 

Personal information is collected only when voluntarily offered and solely for purposes that are clearly identified in this privacy policy notice or at the time you submit your information. At a minimum you will need to provide a name and a credit card number in order to log in. After providing such information, you will be able to navigate freely within the site and read about the benefit and its features. However (for obvious reasons), if you want to file a claim and/or inquire about pending claim, you will have to enter in enough information to enable us to confirm your eligibility for the benefit and establish a claim file or identify the claim about which you are inquiring. 

We will not share your personal information without your consent, except as otherwise set forth in this privacy policy notice and as is necessary in order to provide our products and services to you. To this end, information relating to you and your claim may be shared among Visa and the program partners. The program partners, all of whom are listed in the first portion of this policy, are those companies that provide and administer the Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver. Such information may individually identify you and your claim, or be depersonalized in the aggregate for program related statistical reportings. 

Legal Disclaimer-Instances In Which Your Information May Be Disclosed 

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a government mandate, a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site. In such instances, we will take the utmost care to disclose only that which is subject to such official and/or judicial directive. 

Business Transfers 

If a third party acquires all or substantially all of our assets, your personal information, aggregated information, and any other information that we have collected on this site may be transferred to such third party as part of our business assets. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered one of our assets and may be sold or transferred to third parties. 

Links to Other Web Sites 

Provided for your convenience, our site may contain links to other web sites (such as, Visa.com). Please remember that when you use a link to go from Eclaims to another web site, this privacy policy notice is no longer applicable. Additionally, we are not responsible for, and make no representations with respect to the privacy practices, privacy statements, or otherwise regarding these or any other web sites. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to further understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing your information. 

You Have a Right To Update and Verify The Accuracy Of Information We Collect 

Keeping your information accurate and up to date is important. You have the right to review any personal information about you that we collect, except for information relating to a claims or a criminal proceeding. 

Sweepstakes, Trivia Games, and Surveys 

Eclaims may participate in the offering of sweepstakes, contests, trivia games, or surveys via this web site. Whether or not you enter is entirely at your discretion. If you do, unless otherwise noted in the applicable rules, terms and conditions, or disclaimers, we will use your response in order to select winners, to come up with the game or survey results and, sometimes, to publish those results in aggregate on the site as well as the individual names of winners. Except where necessary to administer a sweepstakes, contests, games, or surveys and to comply with statutory record retention requirements, we will never permanently record or publish any response or information you give connected to your name or address. We will hold these responses and information only as anonymous statistics. 

Contacting Eclaims 

When you send us an email, we use your email address to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question, and we will store your communication and our reply in case we correspond further. Beyond our initial reply, we will never use your email address to send you any unsolicited message or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use. 

Modification of This Privacy Policy 

This policy is developed in the context of evolving and changing Internet technologies. Accordingly, these policies are subject to change. Any changes will be posted on this page and you will be bound by them. 

You May Elect to Not Provide Information to Us Electronically 

You can still take advantage of the Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver benefit that accompanies your Visa membership, even if you elect not to share information with us. In such case, please feel free to call the Auto Rental Claims Center and a specialist will be happy to assist you. (Telephone: 1-866-390-9735). 

We value your privacy and your membership. Accordingly, if you have questions about our privacy policy or procedures, we invite you to contact us by phone (as above), or by email at [privacy@mondialUSA.com](mailto:privacy@mondialUSA.com). 

Eclaims Terms and Conditions of Use

* * *

Eclaims value its relationship with you. The following policy provides details relating to the terms and conditions related to your use of our site. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions set forth below, please discontinue your visit to Eclaims. In such instance, we strongly encourage you to share your concerns or questions with us, by emailing us at [privacy@mondialUSA.com](mailto:privacy@mondialUSA.com). 

The Eclaims site is brought to you by the Benefit Administrator and not by Visa U.S.A. Inc. Visa is not affiliated with Eclaims. Neither VISA nor its affiliates or subsidiaries shall be liable for any losses, damages, nor liabilities incurred by you in connection with Eclaims. 

Copyright 

Except for material in the public domain under United States Copyright Law, all material contained on this web site (including all software, HTML code, as well as other code) is protected by U.S. copyright laws. Except as otherwise expressly provided herein, you may not copy, distribute, transmit, display, reproduce, publish, license, modify, create derivative works from, transfer or sell any material contained on the web site without the prior written consent of the copyright owner. 

You may download or make a reasonable number of copies of materials displayed on the web site for the purposes of reviewing the suitability of these products for your purpose, and making a decision as to whether you will purchase these products. Copying or storing of materials displayed for other than such use is expressly prohibited without prior written permission from Eclaims. 

No Warranties 

ECLAIMS PROVIDES THE SITE AND THE INFORMATION ON AN "AS IS, WHERE IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT MAKE ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR ENDORSEMENTS WITH RESPECT TO THE SITE OR THE INFORMATION, AS TO OPERATION OR ITS USEFULNESS AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. 

Further, in recognition of the inherent volatility of the internet environment and supporting technologies, Eclaims does not represent or warrant that the site will be available and meet your requirements, that access will be uninterrupted, that there will be no delays, failures, errors or omissions or loss of transmitted information, that no viruses or other contaminating or destructive properties will be transmitted or that no damage will occur to your computer system. While we endeavor to maintain the regular operation and safety of the site, you have sole responsibility for adequate protection and backup of data and/or equipment and to take reasonable and appropriate precautions to scan for computer viruses or other destructive properties. 

Similarly, Eclaims is not responsible for and will not be liable to you or anyone else for any damages in connection with an attempted transaction or e-mail sent by you to Eclaims, made either to file an Auto Rental Collision Damage Waiver claim or simply for information. Any unprotected communication over the Internet is, as with communication via any other public medium, such as cellular phones, not confidential, subject to possible interception or loss, and is also subject to possible alteration. 

Modification of Terms and Conditions of Use 

We reserve the right to modify the foregoing terms and conditions of use at our discretion without notice to you. Any changes will be posted on this page and you will be bound by them.
